Kheel, Theodore W. Books and Articles 6021/008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Tour of Duty, 2004; Publication (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Tour of Duty: John Kerry and the Vietnam War, 2004; Publication (Box 10, Folder 23)
    Author: Douglas Brinkley
- Transit and Arbitration, 1960; Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Transit and Arbitration: A Decade of Dicisions, 1960; Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Author: John K. Turcott; Theodore Kheel
    Notes: Includes "The Path to Transit Peace" by J. K. Turcott
  - Item 2: Transit and Arbitration: A Decade of Dicisions, 1960; Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Notes: Includes "The Path to Transit Peace" by J. K. Turcott. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Transit and Arbitration: A Decade of Dicisions, 1960; Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Notes: Includes "The Path to Transit Peace" by J. K. Turcott. Copy 3.
- A Transit Balance Sheet, 1974; Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: A Transit Balance Sheet, 1974; Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Notes: Published in the New York Times, March 17, 1974.
  - Item 2: A Transit Balance Sheet, 1974; Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Notes: Published in the New York Times, March 17, 1974. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: A Transit Balance Sheet, 1974; Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Notes: Published in the New York Times, March 17, 1974. Copy 3.
- A Troubled Sea, 1971; Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A Troubled Sea, 1971; Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Notes: Published in Interplay, v.4:no.1 (1971:Jan.)
- The Ugly Truth About Milton Friedman, 1980; Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Ugly Truth About Milton Friedman, 1980; Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Author: Lyndon H. LaRouche, Jr.; David P. Goldman
- United States Court of Appeals, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: James M. (Yazoo) Smith, Plaintiff-Appellee, v. Pro-Football, Inc. and National Football League, Defendants-Appellants, 1976; Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Author: James C. McKay; Paul J. Tagliabue; C. Michael Buxton
    Notes: Brief of Appellant. Nos. 76-2135 and 76-2136
- United States Supreme Court, 1952; Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: United States of America, Appellant, v. Universal C. I. T. Credit Corporation, George P. Neal, Frank E. Wolfe, and Charles I. Conklin, Appellees, 1952; Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Author: Melbourne Bergerman; Theodore W. Kheel; Aaron Lewittes; Seymour Klwinman; Robert E. Hoppman; James P. Aylward; George V. Aylward; James P. Aylward, Jr.
    Notes: Brief of Appellees. October Term, 1952, no.47.
  - Item 2: United States of America, Appellant, v. Universal C. I. T. Credit Corporation, George P. Neal, Frank E. Wolfe, and Charles I. Conklin, Appellees, 1952; Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Notes: Brief of Appellees. October Term, 1952, no.47. Copy 2.
- The University Club, 1993; Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The University Club, 1993; Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Author: The University Club
    Notes: One Hundred and Twenty-Eighth Year, 1993-1994
- The University Club, 1997; Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The University Club, 1997; Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Notes: One Hundred and Thirty-Second Year, 1997-1998
  - Item 2: The University Club, 1997; Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Notes: One Hundred and Thirty-Second Year, 1997-1998. Copy 2.
- The University Club, 1999; Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The University Club, 1999; Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Notes: One Hundred and Thirty-Fourth Year, 1999-2000.
- The Urban Prospect, 1968; Publication (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Urban Prospect, 1968; Publication (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Author: Lewis Mumford
- Voluntary Labor Arbitration Rules, 1988; Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Voluntary Labor Arbitration Rules, 1988; Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Notes: Including Streamlined Labor Arbitration Rules. As Amended and in Effect January 1, 1988.
  - Item 2: Voluntary Labor Arbitration Rules, 1988; Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Notes: Including Streamlined Labor Arbitration Rules. As Amended and in Effect January 1, 1988. Copy 2.
- Washington Information Directory, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Washington Information Directory, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    Author: Congressional Quarterly
- Websites and Articles, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Newsletter, 2005; Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Author: Association of Joint Labor/Management Educational Programs
    Notes: v.5:no.12 (2005:First Quarter)
  - Item 2: The U.S. Steel Industry: Its Present State and Future Possibilities, 2004; Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Author: Tom Conway
    Notes: Presented at Association of Joint Labor/Management Educational Programs 2004 Conference.
  - Item 3: AFL-CIO to Examine New Strategies, Structures, 2005; Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Author: Communications Workers of America (CWA)
    Notes: March 1, 2005. Printed from CWA website, cwa--union.org, March 3, 2005
  - Item 4: Mailers Campaign at Washington Post Expandes, 2004; Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Notes: November 19, 2004. Printed from CWA website, cwa-union.org, November 23, 2004.
  - Item 5: USWA Members Recognized by Famous Artists, 2004; Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Author: Sean Hayden
    Notes: November 18, 2004. Printed from ILCA website, ilcaonline.org, November 19, 2004.
  - Item 6: USWA Members Recognized by Famous Artists, 2004; Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Notes: November 18, 2004. Printed from ILCA website, ilcaonline.org, November 30, 2004.
- What We Stand For, 2004; Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: What We Stand For: A Program for Progressive Patriotism, 2004; Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Author: Mark Green
    Notes: Authors include: Samuel R. Berger; Ellen Chesler; David Cole; Christopher Edley, Jr.; Richard F. Elmore; James K. Galbraith; Mark Green; Robert Greenstein; Gary Hart; Bruce Katz; Peter Orszag; Ron Pollack; Carl Pope; Jonathan Schell; Mark Schmitt; Joel Seligman; Anne-Marie Slaughter; Christopher Stone
- What's Ahead in Labor Relations, 1963; Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: What's Ahead in Labor Relations, 1963; Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Notes: Published in "Spokes in the Wheel of the Rotary Club of New York" v.1:no.44 (1963:Apr. 30)
  - Item 2: What's Ahead in Labor Relations, 1963; Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Notes: Published in "Spokes in the Wheel of the Rotary Club of New York" v.1:no.44 (1963:Apr. 30). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: What's Ahead in Labor Relations, 1963; Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Notes: Published in "Spokes in the Wheel of the Rotary Club of New York" v.1:no.44 (1963:Apr. 30). Copy 3.
- When Smoke Ran Like Water, 2002; Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: When Smoke Ran Like Water, 2002; Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Author: Derva Davis
  - Item 2: When Smoke Ran Like Water, 2004; Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Notes: Signed by author. Paperback copy. Copy 2.
- Why an Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations, 1928; Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Why an Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations, 1968; Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Notes: For publication in "Lithopinion", March 1968.
  - Item 2: Why an Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations, 1968; Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Notes: For publication in "Lithopinion", March 1968. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Why an Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations, 1968; Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Notes: For publication in "Lithopinion", March 1968. Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Why an Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations, 1968; Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Notes: No author listed, believed to be Theodore Kheel. January 8, 1968.
  - Item 5: Why an Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations, 1968; Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Notes: No author listed, believed to be Theodore Kheel. January 8, 1968. copy 2.
  - Item 6: Why an Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations, 1968; Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Notes: No author listed, believed to be Theodore Kheel. January 8, 1968. copy 3.
- Why the 2.5 Billion Dollar Transportation Capital Facilities Bond Act of 1971 Must Be Defeated, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Why the 2.5 Billion Dollar Transportation Capital Facilities Bond Act of 1971 Must Be Defeated, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Notes: September 28, 1971.
  - Item 2: Why the 2.5 Billion Dollar Transportation Capital Facilities Bond Act of 1971 Must Be Defeated, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Notes: September 28, 1971. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Why the 2.5 Billion Dollar Transportation Capital Facilities Bond Act of 1971 Must Be Defeated, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Notes: September 28, 1971. Copy 3.
- Who's a Fat Cat Now, 1963; Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Who's a Fat Cat Now, 1963; Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Author: Paul Jacobs; Theodore W. Kheel
    Notes: Review of Paul Jacobs' "The State of the Unions" in the "Sunday Herald Tribune"
  - Item 2: Who's a Fat Cat Now, 1963; Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Notes: Review of Paul Jacobs' "The State of the Unions" in the "Sunday Herald Tribune". Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Who's a Fat Cat Now, 1963; Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Notes: Review of Paul Jacobs' "The State of the Unions" in the "Sunday Herald Tribune". Copy 3.
- Who's Who In the East, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Who's Who In the East, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Author: Marquis Who's Who
    Notes: 13th edtion
- Wild Nights: Nature Returns to the City, 2001; Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Wild Nights: Nature Returns to the City, 2001; Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Author: Anne Mathews
- Will Success Foil the Port Authority, 1969; Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Will Success Foil the Port Authority, 1969; Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Notes: Draft, October 23, 1969.
  - Item 2: Will Success Foil the Port Authority, 1969; Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Notes: Draft, October 23, 1969. Copy 2.
- Word and Bond: At the Port Authority Something's Lacking in Both, 1974; Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Word and Bond: At the Port Authority Something's Lacking in Both, 1974; Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Author: Robert M. Bleiberg; Theodore W. Kheel
    Notes: Editorial Commentary in "Barron's" May 6 and 13, 1974.
  - Item 2: Word and Bond: At the Port Authority Something's Lacking in Both, 1974; Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Notes: Editorial Commentary in "Barron's" May 6 and 13, 1974. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Word and Bond: At the Port Authority Something's Lacking in Both, 1974; Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Notes: Editorial Commentary in "Barron's" May 6 and 13, 1974. Copy 3.
- Workforce Distance Learning Foundation, 2000-2006 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: About Our Agency: F.E.G.S is about people, people helping people., 2000; Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Author: FEGS
    Notes: Printed from the FEGS website, January 22, 2000.
  - Item 2: As Teacher in Classroom, Internet Needs Fine-Tuning, 2000; Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Author: Jacques Steinberg
    Notes: July 7, 2000. Printed from the New York Times website, www.nytimes.com, July 7, 2000.
  - Item 3: Education Update, 2000; Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Author: Education Update
    Notes: v.5:no.11 (2000:July)
  - Item 4: The Newsletter, 2006; Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.6:no.13 (2006:First Quarter)
- Working Press of the Nation, 1973; Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Working Press of the Nation, 1973; Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Author: Lou Lauth, Jr.; Elaine White; Mary Burnett
    Notes: v.1: Newspaper and Allied Services Directory
- The World of Professional Golf, 2002; Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The World of Professional Golf, 2002; Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Author: Mark H. McCormack
- Daily Reminder, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Daily Reminder, 1972; Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
    Notes: Theodore Kheel's appointment book.
  - Item 2: Daily Reminder, 1973; Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Daily Reminder, 1974; Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Daily Reminder, 1975-1977 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Daily Reminder, 1975; Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Daily Reminder, 1976; Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Daily Reminder, 1977; Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Daily Reminder, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Daily Reminder, 1978; Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Daily Reminder, 1979; Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Daily Reminder, 1979; Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Notes: Theodore Kheel's appointment book. Copy 2.
- Daily Reminder, 1980; Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Daily Reminder, 1980; Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Daily Reminder, 1980; Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Daily Reminder, 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Daily Reminder, 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Daily Reminder, 1981; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Daily Reminder, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Daily Reminder, 1982; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Daily Reminder, 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Daily Reminder, 1983; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Daily Reminder, 1984-1986 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Daily Reminder, 1984; Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Daily Reminder, 1985; Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Daily Reminder, 1986; Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Daily Reminder, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Daily Reminder, 1987; Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Daily Reminder, 1988; Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Daily Reminder, 1989; Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Daily Reminder, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Daily Reminder, 1990; Publication (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Daily Reminder, 1991; Publication (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Daily Reminder, 1992; Publication (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Daily Reminder, 1993-1995 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Daily Reminder, 1993; Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Daily Reminder, 1994; Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Daily Reminder, 1995; Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Daily Reminder, 1996-1999 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Daily Reminder, 1996; Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Daily Reminder, 1998; Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Daily Reminder, 1999; Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  June 2001.
  - Item 1: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Author: The Earth Times
    Notes: June 6, 2001. Habitate Special Session on Cities.
  - Item 2: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 6, 2001. Habitate Special Session on Cities. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 6, 2001. Habitate Special Session on Cities. Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 7, 2001. Habitate Special Session on Cities.
  - Item 5: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 7, 2001. Habitate Special Session on Cities. Copy 2.
  - Item 6: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 7, 2001. Habitate Special Session on Cities. Copy 3.
  - Item 7: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 8, 2001. Habitate Special Session on Cities.
  - Item 8: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 8, 2001. Habitate Special Session on Cities. Copy 2.
  - Item 9: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 8, 2001. Habitate Special Session on Cities. Copy 3.
  - Item 10: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 25, 2001. UN Special Session on HIV/AIDS.
  - Item 11: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 25, 2001. UN Special Session on HIV/AIDS. Copy 2.
  - Item 12: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 25, 2001. UN Special Session on HIV/AIDS. Copy 3.
  - Item 13: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 26, 2001. UN Special Session on HIV/AIDS. Copy 3.
  - Item 14: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 26, 2001. UN Special Session on HIV/AIDS. Copy 2.
  - Item 15: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 27, 2001. UN Special Session on HIV/AIDS.
  - Item 17: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 27, 2001. UN Special Session on HIV/AIDS. Copy 2.
  - Item 18: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 27, 2001. UN Special Session on HIV/AIDS. Copy 3.
  - Item 19: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 28, 2001. UN Special Session on HIV/AIDS.
  - Item 20: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 28, 2001. UN Special Session on HIV/AIDS. Copy 2.
  - Item 21: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Notes: June 28, 2001. UN Special Session on HIV/AIDS. Copy 3.
- Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  July 2001.
  - Item 1: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Notes: July 19, 2001. Bonn: UN Special Session on Climate Change.
  - Item 2: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Notes: July 28, 2001. National Urban League Annual Meeting.
  - Item 3: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Notes: July 28, 2001. National Urban League Annual Meeting. Copy 2.
  - Item 4: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Notes: July 28, 2001. National Urban League Annual Meeting. Copy 3.
  - Item 5: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Notes: July 29, 2001. National Urban League Annual Meeting.
  - Item 6: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Notes: July 29, 2001. National Urban League Annual Meeting. Copy 2.
  - Item 7: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Notes: July 30, 2001. National Urban League Annual Meeting. Copy 2.
  - Item 8: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Notes: July 30, 2001. National Urban League Annual Meeting. Copy 3.
  - Item 10: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Notes: July 31, 2001. National Urban League Annual Meeting.
  - Item 11: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Notes: July 31, 2001. National Urban League Annual Meeting. Copy 2.
- Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
  August 2001.
  - Item 1: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Notes: August 2, 2001. National Urban League Annual Meeting.
  - Item 2: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Notes: August 2, 2001. National Urban League Annual Meeting. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Notes: August 2, 2001. National Urban League Annual Meeting. Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Notes: August 30, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism.
  - Item 5: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Notes: August 31, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism. Copy 2.
  - Item 6: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Notes: August 31, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism. Copy 3.
- Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  September 2001.
  - Item 1: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 1, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism.
  - Item 2: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 1, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 1, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism. Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 2, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism.
  - Item 5: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 2, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism. Copy 2.
  - Item 6: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 2, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism. Copy 3.
  - Item 7: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 3, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism.
  - Item 8: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 3, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism. Copy 2.
  - Item 9: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 3, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism. Copy 3.
  - Item 10: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 4, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism.
  - Item 11: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 4, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism. Copy 2.
  - Item 12: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 4, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism. Copy 3.
  - Item 13: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 5, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism.
  - Item 14: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 5, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism. Copy 2.
  - Item 15: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 5, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism. Copy 3.
  - Item 16: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 6, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism.
  - Item 17: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 6, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism. Copy 2.
  - Item 18: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 6, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism. Copy 3.
  - Item 19: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 7, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism.
  - Item 20: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 7, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism. Copy 2.
  - Item 21: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 7, 2001. Durban: World Conference Against Racism. Copy 3.
  - Item 22: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 10, 2001. A Decade of conferences: Traveling the bumpy road from Rio: Johannesburg 2002.
  - Item 23: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Notes: September 10, 2001. A Decade of conferences: Traveling the bumpy road from Rio: Johannesburg 2002. Copy 2.
  - Item 24: Conference News Daily, 2001; Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)